Guide to the Alfred E. Kahn papers, 1942-1994
Kahn, Alfred E. papers, 1942-1994
- Series XII. Statements & Testimonies
  - Speech ERG Meetings Washington, DC 3/1/88-3/2/88, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Speech EPRI Atlanta, GA 3/15/88, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Speech NFAEG New York, NY 3/16/88, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Testimony Express Mail USPS, Washington, DC 3/28/88, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Verified Statement Pittston 4/13/88, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Rochester Tel Testimony 2/3/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - AGT Testimony 2/15/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Testimony AGT Reviw of Regulatory Framework 4/13/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Affidavit of Bell Atlantic First 5/28/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Talk Cornell Reunion 6/11/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Article Review of Industrial Organization June, 1993, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Air New Zealand 6/25/93 - 8/19/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Sinclair Testimony 8/12/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Article Regulation Magazine Change, Challenge and Competition Aug., 1993, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Affidavit New Zealand Rail 9/27/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Federal Bar Association's Roundtable Discussion 9/1/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Airline Seminar-Phila. 9/24/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Conference Nera London 10/4/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Talk London IEA Aviation Conference 10/5/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Boces Talk 10/20/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Talk EEI-Florida 11/1/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Testimony AT&T Nondom 11/1/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Testimony C&P/Bell Atlantic 11/19/93, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Testimony C&P/Bell Atlantic 1/10/94, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Testimony Bell Atlantic TCI 1/13/94, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Testimony C&P/Bell Atlantic 1/24/94, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Speech Ontario Hydro Toronto, Ontario 2/8/94, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Keynote Address Naruc Conference(DOE) 2/15/94, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Testimony Mass. Elec. 3/14/94, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Visit Gonzaga Univ. Mar/Apr., 1994, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Testimony BA - New Jersey 4/7/94, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Testimony NYNEX 5/5/94, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Testimony Ameritech 5/12/94, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Testimony SWBell MFJ Waivers 5/12/94, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Keynote Address Opening Ceremonies Airport Council International 10/25/99, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Talk Cornell Club Reception Philadelphia 5/22/94, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - AGT Symposium Emerald Lake Lodge 5/26/94-5/28/94, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Testimony BellSouth First Amendment 6/3/94, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - MGT. Illinois Power Board 6/8/94, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Conf. Nera Telecommunications Call 6/10/94, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Talk Niagra Mohawk 6/14/94, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Talk EEI-Seattle 6/15/94, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Testimony Rochester Telephone 6/17/94, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Testimony Bell Atlantic 6/28/94, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Testimony Rochester Tele. 7/22/94, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Affidavit AT&T - McCAW 9/5/94, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Article The Electricity Journal, Oct., 1994, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - EEI Standard I, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Kraft CASE Judge Kimba Wood, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Testimony Narragansett Electric 11/18/94, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Testimony SNET 1/10/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Testimony SNET Rebuttal 2/13/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Panel Consumer Federation of America 3/17/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Testimony AGT Prcinciples, Rebuttal 3/15/95, 3/30/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Testimony United Illuminating 3/24/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - NYS Public Service Commission Electricity Forum 5/4/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Speech Southern Co. Forum, Atlanta, GA 5/9/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - BA-NJ Testimony 5/31/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Testimony SNET 6/15/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - New Zealand Telecom Officials' Report, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Testimony NYNEX Massachusetts 8/22/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Testimony Pacbell Universal 9/1/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Testimony SNET 9/20/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Affidavit Bell Atlantic (with B. Taylor), Oct., 1995, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Utility Women's Conference Kansas City 10/4/95-10/5/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Santa Babara 10/19/95-10/20/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Testimony Granite State Electronic 10/30/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Speech AEI (American Enterprise Inst.) 11/9/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Talk Illinois Polley Summit Chicago, IL 11/28/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Testimony Bell Atlantic - Pennsylvania 12/7/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - Testimony Pacific FCC CAPS 12/11/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 36)
  - Testimony Bell Atlantic - Maryland 12/21/95, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 37)
  - Testimony Bell Atlantic - Pennsylvania 2/14/96, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 38)
  - Testimony Bell Atlantic - Maryland 2/15/96, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 39)
  - Testimony Bell Atlantic Maryland - Rebuttal 3/14/96, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 40)
  - Testimony Bell Atlantic Maryland - Surrrebuttal 4/1/96, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 41)
  - Talk Ontario Energy Board 4/29/96, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 42)
  - ATA Speeches, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Speech: Issues and Answers to George Meany 10/29/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Alpha Board of Directors Mtg Bal Habour, FA 11/3/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Senate Banking Committee 11/3/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Hartford, CT 11/8/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Speaker Orientation, Anti-Inflation Program, Rm 208 11/9/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Luncheon - Chamber of Commerce 11/16/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Moorhead Committee Testimony 11/22/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Conference on Wage-Price Guidelines 11/27/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Conference on Wage-Price Guidelines 11/28/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Briefing Kentucky State Const. White House 11/28/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Regulation Magazine Nov./Dec., 1978, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Gridiron Club Comments 12/2/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Testimony Subcommittee on Economic Growth & Stabilization 12/6/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Testimony Joint Economic Comm. 12/6/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Briefing National Conference of State Legislatures 12/13/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Business Round Table Briefing 12/14/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - NYC Inflation Briefing 12/19/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Florida Anti-Inflation Telephone Briefing 12/19/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Speeches - 1978, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 20)
  - Testimony Subcommittee on Energy & Power 12/21/78, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Democratic Mini-Convention Dec., 1978, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 22)
  - National Urban Coalition Speech 1/10/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 23)
  - Testimony House Committee on Budget 1/30/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 24)
  - Testimony House Committee on Ways & Means 1/30/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 25)
  - Testimony House Ways & Means Real Wage Insurance 1/30/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 26)
  - Testimony House Budget Comm. General Economy 1/30/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 27)
  - The Florida Council of 100 2/1/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 28)
  - North Carolina 2/1/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 29)
  - Testimony Subcom. Economic Stabilization 2/6/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 30)
  - Testimony Before Subcommittee on Commerce, Cons. & Monetary 2/7/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 31)
  - Consumer Federation Speech 2/8/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 32)
  - Testimony Banking, Housing & Urban Affairs 2/9/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 33)
  - Woman's National Democratic Club Speech 2/12/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 34)
  - Testimony House Committee on Appropriation 2/14/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 35)
  - Reg. Council - W.H. Conf. Small Business 2/15/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 36)
  - Meeting NEA & ILGWU 2/16/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 37)
  - Economic Club of Detroit 2/26/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 38)
  - National Governors' Conference 2/25-27/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 39)
  - Testimony on Environment Pollution (Muskie Senate Comm) 2/27/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 40)
  - Face the Nation 3/4/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 41)
  - Testimony Senate Budget Comm. 3/7/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 42)
  - Lousiana State Legislature Speech 3/8/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 43)
  - Testimony Subcommittee on Health & The Environment 3/12/79, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 44)
  - Speech U/PA Wharton 11/11/86, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Testimony Owners Comm. 11/18/86, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Speech S. Eco. Asso. New Orleans 11/23/86, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Speech CT Society of CPAs Hartford 12/9/86, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Testimony APS 12/19/86, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Testimony INGAA 12/29/86, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Testimony Owners Comm. XE 1/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Speech Merrill Lynch Naples, FL 1/30/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Testimony Public Service of New Jersey 1/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Testimony Central Vermont Cross-Examination 2/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Cornell University Lecture Bob Smiley's Class 2/9-11/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Speech Consumer Federation of America, Washington, DC 2/12/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Article California Law Rev. 2/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - ERG Meetings Washington 2/18-19/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Speech NERA Telecomm. Phoenix 3/7-9/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Testimony APS XE 3/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - Testimony APS Rebuttal 3/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Testimony Airline Mergers Senate Judiciary Comm. 3/25/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - Testimony New York Tel 4/17/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - Speech NY State (Rapp) Telecommunications 4/29/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 20)
  - "Transportation Deregulation…And All That" Econ. Dev. Quarterly 5/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 21)
  - EEI Meeting Washington, DC 5/6/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 22)
  - Speech World Bank Baltimore 5/7/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 23)
  - Talk NJ Governor's Advisory Bd, Trenton 5/7/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 24)
  - Speech Business Week Atlanta 5/20/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 25)
  - Testinomy New York Telephone Albany 6/6/87, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 26)
  - Affidavit Bell Atlantic - Pricing of Input 5/30/96, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Testimony Kansas 6/14/96, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Argentina Trip - June, 1996, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Declaration FCC: Cost Allocation 7/19/96, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Testimony Snow White 8/9/1996, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Article Regulation "Standard Electric Utility Cost" Fall 1996, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Statement US West 10/11/96, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Article Cato Institute FCC Dkt 96-112 Fall 1996, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Ver.Stmt. Coal Rates Surface Transp. Baord 11/27/96, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - A.E.A. Meeting 1/5/97, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - London Trip 1/13/97-1/14/97, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Statement Railroad Revenue Adequacy - Feb., 1997, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Testimony USTA Reform of Carrier Access Charges 2/14/97, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Statement US West Funding & Distr. 3/13/97, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Testimony SNET Reorganization 3/24/97, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - IDA Talk Washington, DC 4/12/97-4/15/97, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Statement PP&L Company 8/4/97, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Cato Luncheon Address 9/12/97, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Testimony Delmarva P&L 10/20/97, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Testimony Conrail/Rail Rates, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Testimony CA. Standards of Conduct 11/17/97, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Testimony Boston Edison 11/21/97, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Testimony Boston Edison Company/RCN 12/22/97, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Testimony Ameren 2/17/98, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Rebuttal Testimony Ameren 3/11/98, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Statement Surface Transportation Board 3/24/98, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Surface Transportation Board Testimony 4/2/98, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Testimony PSE&G NJ 4/16/98, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Testimony Aviation Subcommittee 4/22/98, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - OP ED NYTimes Used & Useful 4/15/84, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - OP ED NYT Trade Deficit 10/10/85, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - OP ED Baltimore Sun Causes & Cures of the Trade Deficit 11/4/85, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - OP ED Ithaca Journal Trade Deficit 11/11/85, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - OP ED NYTimes Airlines Deregulations & Safety 4/14/86, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - OP ED Peoples Exp. NY Times 6/26/86, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - OP ED Washington Post The Demise of People Express 8/26/86, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Deregulation WSJ European Edition 10/2/86, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - OP ED Los Angeles Times Airline Dereg. 4/5/87, 1987 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - OP ED Ithaca Journal Airline Deregulation 5/7/87, 1987 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - OP ED Baltimore Sun Airline Slots 7/2/87, 9/87, 1987 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - OP ED LA Times "The FCC Proposal to Dereg. AT&T." 10/87, 1987 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - OP ED NY Times Special Prosecutor 5/9/88, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - OP ED New York Times Deregulation Anniversary 10/88, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - OP ED New York Times Airfares 8/13/88, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - OP ED New York Times "My $2.76 Herald Tribune" 12/20/90, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - OP ED The Ithaca Journal The Gulf Crisis 1/3/91, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - OP ED New York Times 1/30/91, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - OP ED NYT Foreign Assets 6/91, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - OP ED WSJ 8/7/91, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - OP ED Defense of Airline Deregulation 1/17/92, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - OP ED New York Times 5/17/92, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 22)
  - OP ED WSJ "Clinton Economic Plan" 12/28/92, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 23)
  - OP ED(Brookings) "Regulatory Politics as Usual" Posted on Web 3/21/93, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 24)
  - OP ED Ithaca Journal Alfred Kahn Likes NAFTA 11/15/93, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 25)
  - OP ED Washington Post 2/96, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 26)
  - OP ED Wall St. Journal FCC Cost Allocation 8/6/96, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 27)
  - OP ED The Ithaca Journal Air Dereg./Antitrust 5/14/98, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 28)
  - OP ED Newark Star Ledger "BPU…phone deregulation…" 8/26/98, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 29)
  - OP ED NY Times New Jersey "Competition in Residential Phone Service" 8/30/98, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 30)
  - OP ED "Watch" AAI 12/98, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 31)
  - OP ED Wall Street Journal "Briding Customers…" 12/11/98, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 32)
  - OP ED Ithaca Journal "…'same old juice,' revisited" 11/17/99, 1999 (Box 110, Folder 33)
  - Cornell Chronicle Commentary: On Air Traffic Congestion 12/16/99, 1999 (Box 110, Folder 34)
  - Testimony Telstra,NZ 2/15/00, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 35)
  - OP ED Ithaca Journal "When the Needs of Humanity…" 2/13/01, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 36)
  - OP ED Ithaca Journal "Liberals and Conservatives" 3/15/01, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 37)
  - Ithaca Journal "A Closer Look at the 'Moral Equivalence'" 10/5/01, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 38)
  - OP ED NY Times "Drawing the Line… Understanding & Justifying" 10/5/01, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 39)
  - OP ED Ithaca Journal "China and WTO: A Threat…" 11/19/01, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 40)
  - OP ED WSJ "Unleash the Broadband Economy" 12/13/01, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 41)
  - OP ED New York Times Price Caps Submitted 2/20/02, 2002 (Box 110, Folder 42)
  - OP ED WSJ Price Caps Submitted 2/20/02, 2002 (Box 110, Folder 43)
  - OP ED Ithaca Journal "Taxes, Services, and the Ability to Pay" 4/24/02, 2002 (Box 110, Folder 44)
  - OP ED NY Times "SUNY Tuition…Pres' Econ. Program" Submitted 1/21/03, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 45)
  - OP ED Ithaca Journal "Contradicting Supply-Side Economics" 2/7/03, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 46)
  - OP ED WSJ "Regulatory Politics as Usual" Submitted 3/4/03, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 47)
  - Ithaca Journal "Future of Flight" AEK 12/17/03, 2003 (Box 110, Folder 48)
  - OP ED New York Times FCC Rules/CCA 6/14/04, 2004 (Box 110, Folder 49)
  - OP ED Financial Times 2/15/06, 2006 (Box 110, Folder 50)
  - Testimony Subcommittee on Railroads 4/22/98, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 51)
  - Testimony PEA Code-Comments 6/9/98, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 52)
  - Texas Code of Conduct Comments - AEK 6/19/98, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 53)
  - Testimony BG&E Direct Testimony 7/1/98, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Testimony Payphone Affidavit 7/13/98, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Texas Utilities Rationale for Competitive Electric Utility Industry 7/21/98, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Payphones - Declaration of AEK (Kellogg) 7/24/98, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Exclusionary Airline Pricing AEK Comments for DOT 9/25/98, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Statement - Number Portability (AEK & T. Tardiff) 10/98, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Testimony US West Phoenix Direct 8/14/98, Reply 10/28/98, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Montana Power Code of Conduct Testimony 9/23/98, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Testimony - Boston Edison Co. 11/21/98, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Meeting in Rochester DOT/FAA 2/5/99, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Rebuttal Testimony Boston Edison Co. AEK 2/12/99, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Testimony US West Seattle Reply 3/10/99, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Testimony BG&E Rebuttal 3/22/99, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - New Jersey Affiliate Relations Standards AEK 5/4/99, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Testimony GTE-Bell Atlantic 5/26/99 & 6/10/99, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Testimony US West Phoenix And Seattle 7/23/99, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Testimony Con Ed 9/10/99, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - Talk Notes FTC Workshop 9/13/99, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Testimony Delmarva 11/12/99, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - Testimony Code of Conduct Consumer Energy Co./Detroit Ed. 11/29/99, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - Standard Cost Piece (Spain) 12/15/99, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - Letters to Editor 83, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 22)
  - Letters to Editor 84, 1984 (Box 111, Folder 23)
  - Letters to Editor 85, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 24)
  - Letters to Editor 86, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 25)
  - Letters to Editor 87, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 26)
  - Letters to Editor 88, 1988 (Box 111, Folder 27)
  - Letters to Editor 89, 1989 (Box 111, Folder 28)
  - Clippings 1992, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 29)
  - Testimony Southwest Bell Application for InterLATA in Okla..(271) 2/13/97, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Testimony Pacific 271 3/26/97, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Affidavit SBC Communications Inc. KS 4/97, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Affidavit SBC Communications Inc. OK 4/7/97, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Reply Affidavit SBC Communications Inc. OK 5/27/97, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Testimony Southwestern Bell MO 8/20/97, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Affidavit SWB Oklahoma 2/13/98, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Testimony SWB Kansas - Paragraph Version 2/17/98, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Testimony SWB - Oklahoma 271 4/17/98, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Testimony SWB Filings, 1998-99 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Testimony American Airlines 2/23/00, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Rebuttal Testimony Delmarva/Connectiv 3/29/00, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - "Enhancing Competition for Broadband…" (US Telecom Assoc) Kahn&Tardiff 5/22/00, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - NYS Bar Assoc. - Antitrust 5/00, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Testimony Statement on Airline Predation Senate Antitrust Subcommittee 5/22/00, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Statement Senate Judiciary And Ltr to McCain - Airline Comp. 6/14/00, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Statement Senate Antitrust Issues/Airline Indus. 7/27/00, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - Declaration - AEK FERC - Associated Pipelines 8/31/00, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Testimony Sydney Airport Charges 1/17/01, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Statement Con ED 4/5/01, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - Testimony Verizon NY 5/15/01, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - Statement of AEK Liberman Committee 6/13/01, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - Statement Auckland International Airport 8/10/01, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 23)
  - Testimony American Airlines British Airways AEK 10/19/01, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 24)
  - Declaration A.E.Kahn/T.J.Tardiff Verizon - Broadband 12/18/01, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 25)
  - Statement - AEK Ferc 1/1/02, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 26)
  - Declaration - AEK Verizon NY 2/4/02, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 27)
  - Testimony New Zealand Telecom AEK Statement 4/19/02, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 28)
  - Statement TransGrid - Australia 7/3/02, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 29)
  - Reply Declaration FCC Section 251 7/17/02, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 30)
  - Declaration - Bellsouth, Qwest, SBC, Verizon A.E.Kahn & W.E.Taylor 12/1/02, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 31)
  - Senate Testimony Financial State of Airlines 1/9/03, 2003 (Box 115, Folder 32)
  - Telus - AEK Statement 1/22/03, 2003 (Box 115, Folder 33)
  - SBC IL Statement AEK 5/5/03, 2003 (Box 115, Folder 34)
  - Declaration Verizon AEK & TT 10/4/04, 2004 (Box 115, Folder 35)
  - Reply Declaration Verizon AEK &TT 10/19/04, 2004 (Box 115, Folder 36)
  - OP ED NYTimes Used & Useful 4/15/84, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - OP ED New York Times Airport Congestion 8/84, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - OP ED Wash Post $100 Billion Trade Deficit 8/14/84, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - OP ED Wash Post $100 Billion Trade Deficit 9/84, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Article Baltimore Sun 10/84, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Article WSJ Who Should Pay for Power-Plant Duds? 8/15/85, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Letters to the Editor 1988-90, 1988-90 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Letters to the Editor 1991, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Letters to the Editor 1992-96, 1992-96 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Letters to the Editor 1997-98, 1997-98 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Letters to the Editor 1999-2000, 1999-2000 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - OP Eds, 2001 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Letters to the Editor 2001-2005, 2001-2005 (Box 116, Folder 13)
- Series XIII. Kahn's Subject Files Alpha
  - Kahn-fidential-C.E.A., 1955 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - AEK Calendar Yellow Sheets, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - AEK - Class Notes, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - AEK Speech - Cornell Reception 4/4/2000, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - AEK's Papers, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - AEK - Personal, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - AEK: Writing Plans, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - AT&T/BellSouth, 2007 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Administrated Prices, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Agriculture Policy, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Air New Zealand III, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Air Traffic Control, 2007 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Air Transport Association(1), 2007-08 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Air Transport Association(2), 2006 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Airline Alliances, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Airline Competition Committee, 1998 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Airlines: Consumer Protection, 2007 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Airlines - Current, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Airline Deregulation II, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Airline Deregulation - Europe, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Airline Deregulation - International, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Aviation U.S.-International Policy, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Airlines: Bumping, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Airlines: Code Sharing, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Airlines - Commuters, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Airlines - C.R.S (Computerized Reservation Systems), 1986 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Committee for Study of Competition in the Airline Industry 1/11/99-1/20/99, 1999 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Airline Industry, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Airlines - Fares, 2008 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Airlines - Essential Air Services Program, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 9)